import 'package:nodir_quiz/tools/quiz_model.dart';

List<QuizModel> quizModelEnglish = [
  QuizModel(
      question: "What ____ your name?",
      answerA: "are",
      answerB: "is",
      answerD: "am",
      answerC: "do",
      correctAnswer: "is"),
  QuizModel(
      question: "What ____ you do?",
      answerA: "are",
      answerB: "does",
      answerD: "will",
      answerC: "do",
      correctAnswer: "do"),
  QuizModel(
      question: "How old are ____?",
      answerA: "you",
      answerB: "she",
      answerD: "he",
      answerC: "i",
      correctAnswer: "you"),
  QuizModel(
      question: "____ do you like?",
      answerA: "Laptop",
      answerB: "We",
      answerD: "What",
      answerC: "are",
      correctAnswer: "What"),
  QuizModel(
      question: "how ____ you ____ school?",
      answerA: "do/get",
      answerB: "does/get",
      answerD: "are/doing",
      answerC: "old/are",
      correctAnswer: "do/get"),
];

List<QuizModel> quizModelMath = [
  QuizModel(
    question: "28 + 12 = ?",
    answerA: "39",
    answerB: "40",
    answerD: "41",
    answerC: "42",
    correctAnswer: "40",
  ),
  QuizModel(
    question: "12 + 2 * 6 - 12 / 2 = ?",
    answerA: "18",
    answerB: "12",
    answerD: "6",
    answerC: "20",
    correctAnswer: "18",
  ),
  QuizModel(
    question: "24 - (8 * 2 + 4) / 10 = ?",
    answerA: "4",
    answerB: "2",
    answerD: "6",
    answerC: "22",
    correctAnswer: "22",
  ),
  QuizModel(
    question: "2 + 2 * 2 + 2 / 2 - 6 = ?",
    answerA: "0",
    answerB: "2",
    answerD: "1",
    answerC: "6",
    correctAnswer: "1",
  ),
];

List<QuizModel> quizModelDart = [
  QuizModel(
    question: "output: Hello World!",
    answerA: "print(Hello World!)",
    answerB: "print(\"\$Hello World!\")",
    answerD: "print(\"Hello World\")",
    answerC: "print('Hello World!')",
    correctAnswer: "print('Hello World!')",
  ),
  QuizModel(
    question: "how to parse from String to int?",
    answerA: "parseInt('123')",
    answerB: "Integer.parse('123')",
    answerD: "int.parse('123')",
    answerC: "integer.parse('123')",
    correctAnswer: "int.parse('123')",
  ),
  QuizModel(
    question: "how to add variable 'good' into String",
    answerA: "'i am' + good",
    answerB: "'i am' +\$good",
    answerD: "i am + 'good'",
    answerC: "'i am \$good'",
    correctAnswer: "'i am \$good'",
  ),
];
